http://www.how-to-study.com/privacy-policy.asp

1.         Overview
Thank you for visiting www.how-to-study.com (the "Website") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Website unless you choose to provide that information. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Website.
2.         What Type of Information We Collect
The server on which the Website is located collects and saves only the default information customarily logged by web server software. Such information may include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, and the pages and images requested.
3.         Children's Issues
The Website is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age, and children under such age must not use the Website or services offered on it to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves.
4.         Copyright
The materials found on the Website are protected by United States and other copyright laws, except for works of the United States Government pursuant to 1 U.S.C. Section 105. The selection, arrangement and presentation of all materials (including information in the public domain), and the overall design of the Website are copyright © 2001-2020, SOAR Learning, Inc. Permission is granted to view and print materials from www.how-to-study.com for the non-commercial purpose of viewing, reading and retaining for reference. Any other copying, distribution, retransmission or modification of information or materials on this site, whether in electronic or hard copy form, without the express prior written permission of SOAR Learning, Inc., is strictly prohibited.
5.         Trademarks
The logo (is/are) trademarks or service marks of SOAR Learning, Inc.
6.         No Warranties
www.how-to-study.com DOES NOT MAKE ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR ENDORSEMENTS WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE) WITH REGARD TO THE Website, THE MATERIALS, ANY PRODUCTS, INFORMATION OR SERVICE PROVIDED THROUGH THE Website, OR ANY SITES LISTED THEREIN, AND THE Website WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY COST OR DAMAGE ARISING EITHER DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY FROM ANY SUCH TRANSACTION. THE Website DOES NOT WARRANT THAT IT WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE OR THAT DEFECTS IN IT WILL BE CORRECTED. THE Website IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS, AS AVAILABLE" BASIS.
IN NO EVENT WILL THE Website OR ITS MEMBERS, MANAGERS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS AND THE ASSIGNS OF SAME BE LIABLE FOR (1) ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR INFORMATION, AND THE LIKE) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE Website, THE MATERIALS OR ANY INFORMATION, OR TRANSACTIONS PROVIDED ON THE Website OR DOWNLOADED FROM THE Website, EVEN IF THE Website OR ITS AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR (2) ANY CLAIM ATTRIBUTABLE TO ERRORS, OMISSIONS OR OTHER INACCURACIES IN THE Website, THE MATERIALS AND/OR LISTINGS OR INFORMATION DOWNLOADED THROUGH THE Website. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE Website'S LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
7.         Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless the Website and its members, managers, officers, employees, agents and the assigns of same, from and against any and all loss, costs, expenses (including reasonable attorneys' fees and expenses), claims, damages and liabilities related to or associated with your use of the Website and any violation of this Privacy Policy by you.
8.         Governing Law and Jurisdiction
This Privacy Policy constitutes a contract made under and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Michigan.
9.         Last Update
This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 1, 2020.
10.       Contact Information
Questions or comments regarding the Website should be sent by e-mail via our contact form or by U.S. mail to P.O. Box 480, Lake Orion, MI 48361.
About Us
How-To-Study.com was acquired by StudySkills.com in 2018 as a part of our ongoing commitment to provide study skills resources for students, teachers, and parents. They continue to add new content to the site, so keep coming back. Learn more about Founder/Author Susan Kruger.
Quick Links
Articles
Self-Assessments
About Us
Privacy Policy
Study Tips
Teaching Tips
Study Skills Products
Social:
© 2001-2020 SOAR Learning Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Design and Hosting by Arc Seven Technology
